03 A Nightmare On Elm Street 3 Dream Warriors Horror 1987 720p [ H264-mp4 ] English
[ TICKING ]
[ DOKKEN 'S " INTO THE FIRE " PLAYING LOUDLY ]
♪ I know it 's wrong ♪ ♪ But I can 't turn away ♪
♪ The flames draw near ♪ ♪ They 're telling me to stay ♪
♪ Into the fire ♪
♪ I 'm falling ♪
Are you crazy ? You 'll wake up the whole neighborhood .
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
- Hi , Mom . - Don 't " Hi , Mom , " me .
What are you still doing up ? It 's past 1 .
Just thought I 'd wait for you .
Well , I 'm home . Now you can get to sleep .
Come on , ándale .
Mom , I 'm really not tired .
Kristen , don 't start with me . You know what your shrink said .
He 's full of it .
I 'm not gonna let you get me into an argument , not tonight .
Now get to sleep .
Mom ...
I 'm still having those awful dreams .
MAN : Elaine , where do you keep the bourbon ?
Uh , I 'll be right down .
- Honey , I 've got a guest . - And you don 't wanna keep him waiting .
That 's right , I don 't .
- Good night . - Good night .
GIRLS : ♪ One , two ♪
♪ Freddy 's coming for you ♪
♪ Three , four ♪
♪ Better lock your door ♪
[ BIKE BELL RINGING ]
♪ Five , six ♪
♪ Grab your crucifix ♪
♪ Seven , eight ♪
♪ Gonna stay up late ♪
♪ Nine , ten ♪
♪ Never sleep again ♪
♪ One , two ♪
♪ Freddy 's coming for you ♪
♪ Three , four ♪
♪ Better lock your door ♪
♪ Five , six ♪
♪ Grab your crucifix ♪
♪ Seven , eight ♪
♪ Gonna stay up late ♪
♪ Nine , ten ♪
Hi , what 's your name ?
Kristen . What 's yours ?
[ GIGGLES ]
What is this place ?
[ SCRAPING ]
I gotta go now .
Wait , little girl , don 't go in there !
Little girl !
Little girl ?
[ BIKE BELL RINGING ]
This is where he takes us .
Come on , we 're going .
[ DOOR SLAMS THEN KRISTEN GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Freddy 's home .
[ YELLING ]
[ FREDDY GROWLS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
GIRL : Put me down , you 're hurting me .
[ YELLS ]
[ KRISTEN SCREAMS AND FREDDY LAUGHS ]
Kristen !
Mom ?
[ GROANS ]
REPORTER [ ON RADIO ] : In local news ...
two more teenage deaths have occurred . Both suicides .
County health officials are at a loss to explain this alarming trend .
Nothing like a little cheery news to start the day , huh ?
Yeah . Say , listen , doc .
I got a new theory about all these suicides , right ?
Don 't hold back on us , Max , we need all the help we can get .
Yeah , well , it 's fucked up chromosomes , man .
Think about it , all their parents dropped acid during the ' 60s .
It beats Simms ' theory .
She thinks it 's nothing but sex , drugs and rock ' n ' roll .
- Shit , that 's what keeps people alive . - Heh .
Hi , Taryn .
You don 't look so hot , kid . Are you getting some sleep ?
- I didn 't think so . - Good morning , Dr. Gordon .
Good morning , Jennifer . How are the burns ?
- Regular , menthol , ultra-light . - They 're healing up nicely ?
Yeah , I 've been good .
So , um , when do I get my cigarette privileges back ?
Don 't hold your breath .
- Phillip . - Hey , doc .
- How is he ? - He 's cooling down .
If he continues having these outbursts , I 'll have to have him isolated permanently .
Aw , don 't worry , it won 't come to that .
I , uh ... I read the report on the new staff member .
Oh , what did you think ?
Frankly , I don 't understand ...
why some grad-school superstar is being treated like a seasoned pro .
She 's been doing groundbreaking research on pattern nightmares .
Elizabeth , we don 't need any outside help . I know these kids .
I don 't want some hotshot taking chances with them just so she can get published .
MAN [ ON INTERCOM ] : Dr. Gordon , Dr. Simms to Examination , stat .
Dr. Gordon , Dr. Simms to Examination , stat .
[ KRISTEN SCREAMING ]
This is ridiculous . I know my own daughter .
She 's trying to get attention , that 's all . And I 'm not gonna play her games with her .
Suicide attempt from County General .
- What 's her name ? - Kristen Parker .
She was fine until we tried to sedate her .
[ CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
Watch it , she tore her stitches out .
Kristen , we wanna help you .
- Hold her , hold her . - KRISTEN : Aah !
No , no , no .
I 'm Dr. Gordon . I 'm not gonna hurt you , I wanna help you .
- Why don 't you ... ? - No !
SIMMS : Be careful , Max .
Back off , Max .
Kristen , put the scalpel down .
Nobody is gonna hurt you .
♪ Five , six ♪
♪ Grab your crucifix ♪
♪ Seven , eight ♪
♪ Better stay up late ♪
♪ Nine , ten ♪
♪ Never , never ... ♪
Never sleep again .
Where did you learn that rhyme ?
Tell me about the kids .
Well , they 're survivors in a way .
They 're all severely sleep disordered . Insomnia , narcolepsy , bed-wetting .
- But the nightmares are the common thread . - Right .
They seem to share a group delusion , a bogeyman , for lack of a better word .
They 're so traumatized , they 'll do almost anything not to sleep .
Anything ?
We lost a kid about a month ago to Fairview .
I don 't know where he got the razors , but he cut off his eyelids to stay awake .
- Oh , God . - NEIL : Shook the kids up pretty badly .
Oh , by the way , that was really great work with the new patient .
Pretty smooth for an intern .
I have had some experience with pattern nightmares .
- I 've got to get going . - Okay , well ...
Let me help you with that .
- Thanks . - You 're welcome .
Now , uh , be sure that you check in with Max ...
and he 'll give you the whole 25-cent tour and everything .
- All right , I 'll see you later . - All right .
Oh , um , Miss Thompson ?
- You can call me Nancy . - All right .
You call me Neil , all right ? What was that nursery rhyme all about ?
That was just something that the kids say to keep the bogeyman away .
Anyway , that 's group therapy .
This whole wing is devoted to the program . Um ...
I guess , yeah , you can use this office for the time being , okay ?
- This will be fine . - All right , great .
Because I 'll have you set up in your own space by the end of the week .
Um , the patients ' rooms are down this way .
This is Phillip . We call him " The Walker . "
- Why is that ? - Because I sleepwalk .
Perfectly normal event ...
that our illustrious staff loves to theorize about endlessly .
Phillip , this is Nancy .
Hi , welcome to the snake pit . Heh .
Thanks .
Nice work .
They really ought to be carved out of wood , but they won 't let me have a knife .
I might , you know , pfft !
Um , this lump over here , this is Kincaid .
Now , I want you to take a good look .
He gets thrown in the quiet room so often , you probably won 't see a lot of him .
Ain 't that right , cool breeze ?
Right , I do it so I don 't have to look at your ugly face all the time .
Yeah , I love you too .
Nice meeting you .
Yeah , they 're really good kids but , uh , don 't let them fool you .
They 're dangerous , to themselves and to each other .
Hi , Joey .
Why , thank you .
- Hey , Marcie , how you doing ? - Great .
- These going to C Ward ? - Yeah .
Come on , I 'll walk you down .
See you later , Joey .
Mrs. Parker , was Kristen acting any different ?
Did you notice anything strange before she made the attempt ?
Kristen specializes in strangeness .
I 've spent thousands on psychiatrists .
Did she always have nightmares ?
No , they 've gotten worse since I took away her credit cards .
I 'm serious .
Miss Thompson , I don 't know what you want from me .
Just some answers .
There are other kids involved , not just Kristen .
All good kids , smart kids .
Look , I 'm sorry to hear that but you 're the experts on this , not me .
If I had any insight into any of this , I would share them with you , believe me .
I 'm sure you would .
If you 'll excuse me , I have to get downtown .
I 'll need to get her things .
I have them packed in a suitcase .
Theresa !
I 'll get them , please , I don 't mind .
It 's the first door at the top of the stairs .
[ METAL SQUEAKING ]
[ BIKE BELL RINGING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ SNARLS THEN KRISTEN SCREAMS ]
[ CREAKING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Nancy !
KRISTEN : Nancy !
[ KRISTEN SCREAMING ]
No !
[ FREDDY ROARING ]
- You . - Oh , my God .
Run !
Get us back out , Kristen , do it now .
Aah !
I used to live in this house .
That 's just a house I dream about .
Have you ever done that before , pull someone into your dream ?
When I was a little girl , like 4 or 5 ...
if I had a nightmare , I would always bring my dad in .
The dreams would always get better .
He used to tell me about it the next day . He used to think they were his dreams .
- Ha , ha . - And when did that stop ?
When I was still a kid .
My folks got divorced .
And after a while , I just thought I imagined the whole thing .
I guess I didn 't .
It 's an amazing gift .
The man in my dreams , he 's real , isn 't he ?
He 's real .
Okay , group 's in session . Straight talk only in this room .
Today , I 'd like to start getting us acquainted ...
with our new staff member , Nancy Thompson .
Let 's make her all welcome .
- MAN : Hi , Nancy . - Hi .
- Hi , Nancy . - Hey , Nancy .
Now , you 've already met Phillip and Kincaid and , of course , Kristen .
How about the rest of you all tell Nancy something about yourselves ?
Will , how about you first ?
Hi , I 'm Will Stanton and , um , I 've had a little accident , as you can see .
Ended up in this chair .
Accident , my ass .
I thought this was supposed to be straight talk in here .
Hey , so he took a jump .
At least , he wasn 't sticking needles in his arm with a bunch of lowlifes .
Save it , Kincaid .
- Jennifer ? - JENNIFER : Um , ahem .
I 'm Jennifer Caulfield .
And , um , as soon as I get out of here , I 'm going to Los Angeles to be an actress .
I 'm gonna be on TV .
Yeah , Lifestyles of the Rich and Psychotic .
Screw you .
[ KIDS LAUGHING ]
This is Joey .
He used to be a debater in school , but now he doesn 't talk much .
TARYN : I 'm Taryn White .
The only reason I 'm in here is because it 's a better deal than juvie hall ...
also , because I 'm going through some very strange shit .
Your dreams ?
Hey , everybody has bad dreams .
Can I interject something here just to save us all some time ?
NEIL : Sure , Phillip , go ahead .
Well , according to our kind hosts ...
our dreams are a group psychosis , sort of a mellow mass hysteria .
The fact we dreamt about this guy before we met doesn 't seem to impress anybody .
KINCAID : Yeah . TARYN : That 's right .
So we go in circles , making minimal progress with maximum effort .
You won 't make any progress until you recognize your dreams for what they are .
And what are they ?
The by-products of guilt .
Psychological scars , stemming from moral conflicts and overt sexuality .
Oh , great , now it 's my dick that 's killing me .
[ KIDS LAUGHING ]
TARYN : Tell me what 's supposed to be happening again .
Okay , you 're being attacked by the bog demon . Go ahead .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
- Uh , 14 . - Doesn 't count .
You got to say the words .
This is stupid .
Oh , come on .
In the name of Lowrek , Prince of Elves , demon , begone .
Good , you conquered the demon but your horse is sinking in the bog .
What do you do ?
I go to bed ...
and get a new horse in the morning .
Well , how do I score that ? Enchanted slumber or death ?
All right , fellas , lights out .
- Oh , Max . - MAX : " Oh , Max . "
You know the rules .
- Yeah . - Come on , Joey , you too .
Every time we get a good game going ...
- it 's always lights out . - Mm-hm .
Okay .
- Good night , fellas . - Good night , Max .
Okay , you get first shift tonight .
Oh , come on , I had it last night .
Good , just remember , keep your eyes open .
And one whimper and you wake me up , okay ?
- This is nice . - You 've never been here before ?
No , um , I think they opened this when I was at school .
Best Thai food in Springwood .
Of course , it 's the only Thai food in Springwood .
Uh , do your parents still live around here ?
My mother passed away .
She , uh , died in her sleep .
I 'm sorry .
My father and I , um ...
Well , things just seemed to fall apart after that .
Sounds like a rough time .
It was .
Neil , what if I told you ...
that , um , your patients are in real physical danger from their dreams .
The nightmares are nothing but a symptom of the real problems .
All right , well , then let 's just eliminate the symptom for the time being .
- With Hypnocil ? - That 's right .
You want me to prescribe ...
an experimental psychoactive drug to a bunch of suicidal teenagers ?
Just until we get things under control .
Dream deprivation is nothing to fool around with .
You have no business taking it yourself .
I used to be like them , Neil . I know what they 're going through .
So do l .
You told me they were survivors and they all are .
But how much longer they survive is up to us .
I 'm sorry , Nancy .
The answer is no .
- Shh . - Ah ... !
[ GROANING ]
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
[ PH lLLIP GROANING ]
Phillip .
Phillip , wake up .
Have a nice stroll , asshole .
[ GROANING ]
What ? What are you doing ?
Hey , come on , man .
What , are you crazy ?
Oh , shit , what is he doing ?
Get help ! Get help !
Phillip ! Phillip !
Phillip , no !
Joey ?
What 's the matter ?
WILL : Phillip ! Phillip !
Phillip ! Phillip , no !
Phillip , no !
Don 't do it , no !
Phillip , don 't do it ! Phillip !
Goddamn !
Phillip !
- Phillip ! - Phillip !
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
- Don 't jump ! - Phillip , don 't jump !
[ GROANING ]
KRISTEN : Phillip !
- Don 't you jump ! - Aah !
[ PH lLLIP YELLING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ CRYING ]
I want us to talk about what happened last night .
I want us to all get our feelings out in the open .
He wasn 't strong enough so he got wasted , that 's all .
That 's all ? Is that what you think ?
He couldn 't hack it so he got nailed , period .
Oh , yeah , big , tough bad ass . How long are you gonna last ?
I 'm gonna last longer than any of you .
Well , just go ahead and fight because that 's what he wants .
- Who ? - Who do you think ?
What does he want ?
To turn us against each other so we 'll be weak , easy prey .
- KINCAID : Horse shit . - No , she 's right .
I think we 're all missing the point here .
Phillip 's death was a sleepwalking accident , nothing more .
No .
I could see him up there .
His face ...
He was wide awake all the way down .
Well , then it was suicide . Phillip quit , he gave up .
Joey says it wasn 't suicide .
Listen to me , Joey , Phillip killed himself .
Now , that 's a cowardly thing . That 's an empty thing .
He let himself down . He let all of us down .
It was murder . Can 't you understand that ?
That bastard murdered him !
I 'm not gonna listen to any more of this .
How much longer are you going to go on ...
blaming your dreams for your own weaknesses ?
- How much longer you gonna keep throw ... - That 's enough , Kincaid .
There will be no repeat occurrences of last night 's events .
From now on your doors will be locked during sleeping hours .
We 'll start a policy of evening sedation for everybody .
The fuck you will . Anybody who tries drugs on me , gets his ass kicked .
You just bought yourself a night in the quiet room , mister .
- Now , sit down . - Fuck you , you sit down .
- Easy , Kincaid . - KINCAID : Nobody is gonna put me to sleep .
Get away from me . Leave me alone .
I don 't wanna go to sleep . Nobody gonna put me to sleep .
Get your hands ... I ain 't gonna sleep .
Stay in your seats .
KINCAID : Get your hands off me , I don 't wanna ...
We 'll begin sedation tonight starting with him .
You can 't . They 'll be defenseless against their dreams .
That 's precisely what they need .
Some uninterrupted REM sleep to release all that negative energy .
Elizabeth , I 'm prescribing Hypnocil . It 's a dream suppressant .
I know what it is . I just can 't believe what I 'm hearing .
- What has she talked you into ? - Nothing .
My patients , my decision .
I want these dreams stopped till we get some answers .
I can 't allow that .
Then I 'll go straight to Carver if I have to .
And he 'll either back me up or accept my resignation .
All right .
But if something goes wrong , I 'll make sure that you 're held responsible .
I mean that . Fully responsible .
I can 't believe I just said that .
Do you think we can get the Hypnocil by tomorrow ?
We 're gonna try .
I hope you know what you 're getting us into .
[ SINGING ] ♪ Ain 't gonna dream no more , no more ♪
♪ Ain 't gonna dream no more ♪
♪ All night long , I sing this song ♪
♪ - April ! ♪ ♪ - He shot me with a slingshot ! ♪
♪ - I did not ! ♪ ♪ - Liar ! ♪
WOMAN : April . GIRL : Liar .
MAN : Hold it , hold it .
- Girl , what are you doing ? - Watching TV .
I can see that .
Why don 't you read a book ? You watch too much damn TV .
Research .
Oh , right , you 're gonna be a TV star .
Wait and see .
Yeah , well , if Simms catches you here after lights out , she 's gonna chew my ass .
- I got to stay up , Max . - Jennifer .
Just tonight , please .
I can 't handle the nightmare .
Not after Phillip , not tonight .
Okay .
But I never saw you .
- Thanks , Max . - Okay .
BOY [ ON TV ] : This is a great meal , Mrs. Brown ...
really one of the best I 've ever had .
WOMAN : Thanks , thank you , Steve .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Hi , sweet stuff , good news .
It can 't be good news coming from you .
I pulled night duty .
- So ? - So got the keys to heaven , baby .
- What ? - The dispensary .
I am talking clean pharmaceutical high , a night at Club Meth .
- I don 't do that shit . - Yeah ?
- What are those , beauty marks ? - Those are ancient history .
Oh , yeah ?
Well , if you 're ever in the mood for a history lesson ...
I 'm your teacher , understand ?
Stay out of my face or I 'll go straight to Max .
Oh , yeah ?
Now , who 's gonna take the word of a crazy junkie chick like you ?
Fuck off !
[ LAUGHING ]
MAN [ ON TV ] : Hon , I kind of figured you 'd watch me bowl tonight .
We 're defending the championship , you know ?
- Oh , we 're ... - WOMAN : Maybe we 'll come by later .
Don 't suppose anybody would like some dessert before they leave .
GIRL : No , thanks , Mom . MAN : No , it was very good .
- Thank you . - WOMAN : Thanks .
MAN : Helen ? WOMAN : Hmm ?
MAN : Have you , you know , talked to her about the way things are ?
WOMAN : Years ago .
MAN : Years ?
BOY : What do I want to see an old barn for ?
- GIRL : Come on , it 's romantic . - Aah ! Unh .
BOY : Look , April .
GIRL : You want your car keys back , don 't you ?
- - silly thing to ask you , but how many of what did they have to kill ?
GABOR : Don 't say that because I love animals .
I 've seen animal shelters .
I bought it only red with black in it , so I didn 't know what it was .
- Probably from an artificial bird . - GABOR : Ha .
CAVETT : Did you ever go to any kind of acting school ?
GABOR : Not in the beginning . I started on a talk show .
When a young actress says , " How do you succeed in this ? "
- You don 't always say study ? - Study .
I think you should study .
They have to study , work .
And then maybe you can make it .
- Can I ask you something ? - Certainly .
Who gives a fuck what you think ?
[ SCREAMS ]
GIRL [ ON TV ] : This is your break , Jennifer .
[ DISTORTED SCREAMING ]
♪ One , two ♪
♪ Freddy 's coming for you ♪
♪ Three , four ♪
♪ Better lock your door ♪
♪ This is your break , Jennifer . ♪
♪ This is your break , Jen ... ♪
[ SCREAMING ]
- This is it , Jennifer , your big break in TV . - Aah !
- Welcome to prime time , bitch ! - Aah !
Don 't be ashamed , young man .
This is a place for sorrow .
What faith do you follow ?
Science , I suppose .
Sad choice .
There are times when it doesn 't offer much comfort .
I 've seen you before , uh , Sister ... ?
Mary Helena .
You do volunteer work at the hospital .
From time to time , when I 'm needed .
I should have been able to save them .
Only one thing can save the children .
The unquiet spirit must be laid to rest .
It is an abomination to God and to man .
NANCY : Neil .
Excuse me , Sister .
What are you doing up here ?
Uh , I was just talking to ...
NANCY : To who ?
Doesn 't matter .
- Are you ready to go now ? - Sure .
Are you finished ?
Yeah , I 'm sorry . I guess I , uh ... I 'm not hungry .
That 's okay .
That 's pretty . What is it ?
This is my Malaysian dream doll .
It 's supposed to bring good dreams .
Could use some of that right about now .
You know , I used to think ...
I could do something for the kids , make some kind of difference .
But they 're slipping through my fingers , every one of them .
You 're doing the best you can for them , Neil .
Am I ?
I 'm running out of answers .
A patient sleepwalks out of a high-security ward .
A girl alone in a room dies .
I can 't believe this is happening .
Nothing makes any sense .
Then maybe you 're ready .
For what ?
The truth .
Try me .
Only if you 're willing to put aside everything you 've learned and trust me .
Can you do that ?
I can do that .
Okay .
Straight talk only in this room .
Is this group ?
Well , yeah , unofficially .
Pretty soon , there won 't be enough of us left to call it " group . "
Okay , listen up , you guys .
Nancy has something to say .
I know who 's trying to kill you .
Don 't humor us . We 're not in the mood .
He wears a dirty , brown hat .
He 's horribly burned .
He has razors on his right hand .
Who is he ?
His name is Freddy Krueger .
He was a child murderer before he died .
And after he died ...
well , he became something worse .
Six years ago , he killed my friends .
He almost killed me .
Why is he after us ?
Yeah , what did we do ?
It 's not you .
Your parents , my parents , they burned him alive .
And now we 're paying for their sins .
You are the last of the Elm Street children .
WILL : Mom and Dad ?
I mean , that 's crazy . They never mentioned anything ...
Oh , sure , that 's the sort of thing parents tell their kids .
" Good night , darling , say your prayers .
And , oh , by the way , your father and I torched some maniac last night . "
So what do we do about this creep ?
Kristen is the key .
She has a very special talent , a gift .
I haven 't been able to do that since I was a little girl .
You did it the other night .
That was different .
NANCY : You never lose a gift like that . You just forget how to use it .
How about it , will you try ?
All of you have this inner strength .
Some special power that you 've had in your most wonderful dreams .
Together , we can learn to use that power if we try .
You sound like Peter Pan .
Remember , open mind .
Okay .
Uh , Taryn , would you pull the shades down please ?
We 're gonna try a little , uh , group hypnosis .
I want you all to follow this pendulum with your eyes .
Tune out everything else .
Nothing else exists but the pendulum .
Take us there , Kristen .
NEIL : Breathe deeply and relax .
Starting with your toes , relax everything till there 's no tension left in your bodies .
Keep following the pendulum .
You find yourselves getting tired .
Nothing would feel better right now ...
than a nice , long , deep sleep .
I 'm gonna count backwards from five .
When I finish ...
you will all be asleep .
Five .
Four .
Three .
Two .
One .
Sorry .
That 's okay , we 'll try again .
Everybody take five . Ahem .
I was willing to go through with this for the kids ' peace of mind and yours ...
but you 're gonna have to face reality .
[ WHEELS SQUEAKING ]
[ KIDS CHATTERING QUIETLY ]
WILL : No , I 'm serious , I happen to be very susceptible to hypnosis .
- I 've been told by professionals . - TARYN : What professionals ?
Where are these professionals ?
WILL : Well , " professionals " as in , like , magic-users and illusionists .
Listen , Joey , I just wanted to get you alone for a second .
I mean , look , I really like you .
Do you like me ?
I know this sounds crazy ...
but I make up excuses to come into the ward every day just to see you .
You 're so cute .
Neil , let 's just try one more time .
If it doesn 't work , I promise I 'll ...
We 're here .
Where here ?
We 're in the dream .
Well , no , we 're not . We 're still here in the group .
In my dreams , I can walk .
My legs are strong .
In my dreams , I am the wizard master .
Try something , Kristen . What can you do in your dream ?
[ ALL CHEERING ]
A perfect score . The crowd goes wild . Ahh !
- Ha , ha ! - Fucking A , dig this .
Kincaid , please .
That 's very unnerving .
Hey , check out Taryn .
In my dreams , I 'm beautiful ...
and bad .
Look , I could get into a lot of trouble for this .
But I know you won 't say anything , will you ?
Unzip me .
Do you like my body , Joey ?
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SNARLS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
What 's wrong , Joey ?
Feeling tongue-tied ?
[ LAUGHING ]
Aah !
What 's happening ?
- He 's close . - Who ?
- Freddy ? - He 's out in the halls .
- Where 's Joey ? - Freddy 's got him .
Aah !
Quiet , everyone , listen .
[ LOW RUMBLING ]
The room 's changing .
What the heck is going on ?
- Doctor ... - What 's happening ?
NEIL : Get away from the wall !
[ ALL YELLING ]
Don 't panic ! Quiet down !
Aah !
Help ! Help !
- This isn 't real ! - Dr. Gordon !
- No ! - It 's not !
Quiet , the door .
What 's going on in here ?
What 's wrong with Joey ?
Joey .
- Code blue . - Oh , my God .
[ MACHINE BEEPING ]
He 's in a deep coma . There 's nothing we can do for him .
This is inexcusable .
The session was unauthorized .
It was purposely conducted without my knowledge .
Unusual steps were called for , Dr. Carver .
Is that what I should tell that young man 's parents ?
I understand you prescribed a highly experimental drug .
Dr. Carver , he 's not in a coma because of ...
Young lady , your opinion is of no interest to me .
Furthermore , according to Dr. Simms ...
you 've been creating panic among the patients .
- That 's not true . - Dr. Gordon .
In the last four days , we 've had two suicides .
Now that young man is in a coma .
I think it 's safe to say that your approach has failed , entirely .
You 're both relieved of duty . I want you out of here today .
I 'm sorry , Neil . I 'm afraid you brought it on yourself .
For God 's sake , Elizabeth , please . Will you please just try to help the kids ?
Will you listen to them ?
Of course , I will .
What are we going to do ?
There is nothing that we can do . It 's out of our hands .
Sister !
Sister ?
Hello ?
This is where it began .
This wing has been closed for years .
What was this place ?
Purgatory .
Fashioned by the hands of men .
Twisted , lonely souls .
The worst of the criminally insane ...
were locked up in here like animals .
This whole facility was shut down in the ' 40s , wasn 't it ?
Some sort of scandal ?
A young girl on the staff ...
was accidentally locked in here over the holidays .
The inmates kept her hidden for days .
She was raped hundreds of times .
When they found her , she was barely alive ...
and with child .
That girl was Amanda Krueger .
- Her child ... - Freddy .
The bastard son of a hundred maniacs .
Some say he was murdered ...
though no body was ever found .
You said something before about laying him to rest .
You must find the remains ...
and bury him in hallowed ground .
Hallowed ground ?
Sister ?
If your only faith is science , doctor ...
it may be you that 's laid to rest .
Wait ! Sister !
Let go of him , you bastard .
Oh , my God .
NANCY : I 've got to go in . We don 't have a choice .
Getting yourself killed won 't help the kids at all .
Besides , we do have a choice .
Well , assuming your mysterious nun is right .
I 've heard weirder things this week .
All right .
Whoever she is , she does seem to know more about Krueger than I do .
The question is , what happened to his body ?
They burned him to death in his boiler room and they hid the remains .
Who would know where they 're hidden ?
Well , only one man knows .
And it 's time for him to talk .
No !
You can 't take Nancy away from us !
You can 't ! She 's all we have !
You 're a sick girl , Kristen .
If you wanna get better , you must trust me now .
[ GRUNTING ]
No !
- No , no ! - Take her to the quiet room and sedate her .
- Take it easy . - You stupid bitch , you 're killing us !
You 're killing us !
No !
All right , everybody , back to bed .
KRISTEN : No ! No !
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
Hi , Daddy .
Well , if it isn 't my little girl .
My baby come to see her daddy , huh ?
- It 's been a long time . - Yeah .
But you 're here , sit down .
What did I do to , uh , get so lucky ?
I thought that you were trying to forget me .
That 's not true . You 're the one who 's trying to forget .
Oh , come on .
I need your help , Dad .
Krueger is back .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Fred Krueger is dead .
You always had a little trouble trying to understand that , sweetheart .
You know what he did .
He 's doing it again .
She 's telling you the truth .
I don 't believe we 've ever met , friend .
And I don 't think this is any of your god-damn business .
I think we can stop him this time . Stop him for good .
But we need to know where his bones were hidden .
I 've lost too much over this already .
I 'm through with it .
People are still dying after all this time .
Stop running away from it .
You owe me .
It was nice seeing you again , princess .
Next time , don 't stay away so long .
Nancy ?
- Nancy . - I 'll be okay , just give me a minute .
[ BEEPER BEEPING ]
That 's the hospital .
[ PHONE RINGS ]
- Dr. Gordon ? - NEIL : Taryn ?
You 've got to come right away . It 's Kristen , she had a total shit attack .
Simms doped her up , put her in the quiet room .
Simms put Kristen in the quiet room for the night . They sedated her .
Oh , no .
She can 't stay awake for long . She 's all alone in there .
Freddy is gonna get her .
Okay , none of you panic , just stay cool .
Help is on the way .
- Just hurry . - Okay .
- We better get there now . - You go , I gotta get the remains .
- It 's no use . You see him . - I 'll talk , you get to the hospital .
- Make Simms understand . - She 'll never .
I got to get to Kristen somehow .
Nancy , be careful .
My name is Neil Gordon . Pleased to meet you .
There , now we 've met .
Now , listen to me !
I don 't know if you care whether Nancy lives or dies but I do !
You and I are going on a little scavenger hunt .
Please , God .
Don 't make me sleep .
What the hell are we doing here ?
Hey . Hey !
I won 't be long .
- What do you think you 're doing ? - Uh ...
Look , uh , sorry . Heh .
I really need this . I got , uh ...
I 'll reimburse you .
Here , you can keep my driver 's license . I 'll be back .
[ DINGS ]
Max , I need to see Kristen .
You don 't understand .
Look , Miss Thompson , save your breath . Dr. Simms gave me specific instructions .
No one gets to see Kristen , especially you .
But Max , she needs me , she 's in danger . You got to believe me .
Listen , I really think you mean well , I do . But my kids have been dying off .
And even if I didn 't have orders from Simms ...
I wouldn 't let you near her , no way .
Okay , Max , I understand .
- Can I say goodbye to the others ? - I don 't know .
It will be my last chance .
Okay , you got five minutes . They 're in the TV room .
Where have you been ? We 've been going crazy .
- Shh ! There 's no time for that , come on . - WILL : Where ?
Our last group .
All right .
In there .
We knew nobody would ever find it in that place .
I 'm not sure I can find it myself anymore .
All right , it 's deep in the heart of the place .
Take it slow .
Straight talk only in here .
What about Kristen ?
We can 't get to her , I tried .
I was hoping we would have more time to learn to use the dreams .
But Joey is in there . And Kristen is going in with or without us .
They need us .
You mean , we 're gonna try to go in with her ? To link up ?
It 's now or never .
I 'm not gonna kid you . This is as dangerous as it gets .
If you die in this dream , it 's for real .
Nobody has to go in that doesn 't want to .
I 'm in .
Me too .
Let 's go kick the motherfucker 's ass all over dreamland .
- Yeah . - Ha , ha .
So remember , we have to stay together whatever happens .
It 's the only way we can beat him .
All right , clear your mind of everything .
Picture yourself in the quiet room ...
the soft white walls , the total silence .
Only the sound of your heart beating .
Picture yourself there with Kristen .
I 'm gonna count backwards from five .
And when I 'm done , we 'll all be asleep .
We 'll all be in the quiet room .
Five .
Four .
Three .
Two .
One .
Nancy , heh , I knew you would come .
You don 't think we 'd let you go in alone , do you ?
- No way , we are a team . - WILL : Yeah .
Listen , everybody , Joey needs us . I can feel him .
Where is he ?
How do we find him , Kristen ?
[ ALL YELLING ]
NANCY : Stay in the middle of the room !
No matter what happens , stay together !
KRISTEN : Help ! TARYN : Nancy !
Help me !
[ DOKKEN 'S " INTO THE FIRE " PLAYING ]
Into the fire
Honey , you 're gonna wake up the whole neighborhood .
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
What are you still doing up ? It 's past 1 .
I ...
I just thought I 'd wait for you .
Well , I 'm home . You can get to sleep now .
Come on , ándale .
[ LAUGHING ]
What 's that for ?
I 'm just glad you 're home .
Mom , I had the most awful dream .
MAN : Elaine , where do you keep the bourbon ?
I 'll be right down .
Kris , I 've got a guest .
Please , Mom , I just don 't wanna be alone .
Aah !
- I said , where is the fucking bourbon ! - Mom !
You should listen to your mother .
Goddamn it , Kristen , you ruin everything . Every time I bring a man home , you spoil it !
You know what your shrink says , you 're just trying to get attention !
[ SCREAMING ]
Nancy !
Kristen !
Is that you ?
Welcome home , Taryn .
Look familiar ?
Okay , asshole , let 's dance .
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
Taryn , Taryn , Taryn .
Why ... ? Why should we fight ?
We 're old friends , you and I , remember ?
Let 's get high .
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
What a rush .
[ TARYN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE ]
Hello ?
You guys , where are you ?
Is somebody there ?
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
[ CLATTERING ]
Oh , Will .
You look tired .
Have a seat .
No , thanks . I 'm fine just the way I am .
For now maybe .
But when you wake up ...
it 's back in the saddle again .
My leg !
It 's the chair for you , kid .
I am the wizard master .
I am the wizard master !
In the name of Lowrek , Prince of Elves , demon , begone .
[ GRUNTING ]
Sorry , kid . I don 't believe in fairy tales .
[ SCREAMING ]
KRISTEN : Hello ?
Somebody ?
Hello .
- Kristen ! - Nancy ! Aah !
[ WOOD CRUNCHING ]
- What is that ? - I don 't know .
Yo , I thought I heard voices .
Kincaid , I could kiss you .
- What 's stopping you ? - Mm !
Cool . So where 's Joey ?
I don 't know . This place is like a maze .
Then it 's time to stop guessing and start messing .
Yo , Freddy !
- Where you hiding , you burnt-face pussy ? - Hey , we should find the others first .
You think you 're hot shit with a mute kid , don 't you ?
Well , let me see you come get a piece of me .
Krueger ! Pussy !
I knew he was a little chicken .
[ BANG ]
Shit .
NANCY : It 's a door .
KINCAID : But it doesn 't go anywhere .
Yes , it does .
NANCY : This is it .
Are you ready ?
Let 's snuff the sucker .
That 's it .
The Caddy .
Going somewhere ?
Look , I said I 'd show you where the god-damn thing was .
- I never said I 'd stick around . - We 've got work to do .
- What are you talking about ? - You 're about to attend a funeral .
One that 's long overdue .
Joey !
[ HIGH-PITCHED SCRAPING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Joey .
Look , all the little piggies come home .
Let him go , Krueger !
Your wish is my command .
- No ! - Joey !
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Nancy .
He 's strong . He 's never been this strong .
Yes , sir .
The souls of the children give me strength .
- No . - Unh .
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
Always room for more .
- What 's that ? - What ?
[ CLATTERING IN DISTANCE ]
Listen .
Somebody else is out here .
No .
We 're alone .
[ ENGINE CHUGGING ]
[ HORNS HONKING ]
Bury the fucking thing !
Agh !
It 's really you .
I killed you once before , you son of a bitch .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ YELLS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
NANCY : Let 's try this way .
Kristen , can you pull us out ?
They sedated me . We 're stuck here .
It 's a dead end .
What the hell ?
Sorry to keep you waiting .
Perhaps if there was more of me to spread around .
[ LAUGHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ YELLING ]
[ SHOUTING ] No !
Wow , did I say that ?
- You found your dream power , man . - KRISTEN : You saved us , Joey .
- Man , you blew him away . - Put me down , man .
- Are you okay ? - I think so .
He 's gone .
It 's over . Ha , ha .
THOMPSON : Nancy .
Daddy ?
I 've crossed over , princess .
Crossed over ?
I couldn 't go without telling you how sorry I am for all the things I 've done .
I love you so much .
I 'll always love you .
[ SCREAMING ]
Die .
Nancy .
[ GRUNTS ]
You 're mine now , little piggy !
- No ! - Unh , agh !
[ GRUNTING ]
Please , God , for the children , for Nancy .
Ashes to ashes .
[ SCREAMING ]
Dust to dust .
May the spirit rest .
[ MOANS ]
I won 't let you die . I won 't let you .
I 'm gonna dream you into a beautiful dream ...
forever and ever .
[ MOANING ]
Trust in him at all times , O people .
Pour out your hearts to him , for God is our refuge .
Hear my cry , O God . Listen to my prayer .
From the ends of the earth , I call to you .
I call as my heart grows faint .
Lead me to the rock that is higher than I.
For you have been my refuge .
A strong tower against the foe .
I long to dwell in the tent forever and take refuge in the shelter of your wings .
Even though we entrust Nancy to the earth , her courage and spirit shall remain with us .
For the Lord , God , has comforted us saying ...
that whoever finds his life will lose it ...
and whoever loses his life for my sake will find it .
They shall live forever in the glory of his kingdom .
May the Lord bless you and keep you .
May the Lord make his face to shine down upon you and be gracious to you .
May the Lord turn his face toward you and give you peace .
My God .
You were his mother .